<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">"Discover Suceava "</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">In order to have access to your personal Travel Journal you must Sign in/Sign up</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip registration! </string>
    <string name="sign_up">Join now! It is free!</string>
    <string name="email">Email:</string>
    <string name="screen_name">Screen name:</string>
    <string name="password">Password:</string>
    <string name="sign_up_button">Sign up</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Welcome back!</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button">Sign in</string>
    <string name="dialog_message">If you don\'t have an account, you have to sign up!</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">Alert!</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="sign_in_ok_button">Ok</string>
    <string name="sign_in_message_first">You are now signed in as  </string>
    <string name="sign_in_message_second"> .You can sign out in Settings.</string>
    <string name="sign_in_title">Sign In Alert!</string>
    <string name="check_in_button">Check In</string>
    <string name="map_button">Map</string>
    <string name="thoughts_button">Add your thoughts here and remember them after your trip!</string>

    <!-- DRAWER -->
    <string name="unknown">Loading...</string>
    <string name="obsTime">Observation Time: </string>
    <string name="temperature">Temperature in Suceava: </string>
    <string name="about_app">Discover Suceava is an application that helps tourists to find out about the most important and frequented 
        places in Suceava city: hotels, shopping centers, restaurants and several point of interest. Having a trip journal requires an account.
        Without one, the application user cannot check-in to any of Suceava\'s points of interest. Also, to have acces to Map, Weather and 
        Currency facilities, an internet connection is required.</string>
    <string name="logout_button">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_exit">Exit</string>

    <string-array name="drawer_items">
        <item>About App</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Feedback</item>
        <item>Currency</item>
        <item>Weather</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="menu_items">
        <item>Map</item>
        <item>Food and Drink</item>
        <item>Hotels</item>
        <item>Attractions</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
        <item>My Trip Journal</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- FOOD AND DRINK -->
    <string name="fd_image">Image for food and drink</string>
    <string name="padrino_desc">If you are looking for good food and service in Suceava go here. The decorations are clear and well selected.
         The menu is full of good options to select from. There are plenty of events to choose from too.</string>
    <string name="padrino_contact">Str. Universitatii, Nr. 14, Suceava </string>
    <string name="padrino_contact2">Phone:0330 112 116</string>
    <string name="padrino_contact3">Schedule: M-F:9.00 am - 1.00 am , Weekend: 9.00 am - 6.00 am</string>
    <string name="taco_loco_desc">This restaurant is situated in the heart of Suceava and here you can find from traditional to international food at a great price too.
        The staff is always polite and friendly, never in a hurry. 
        The seating area outside is great. Not only that the place is beautiful and the service is polite but the food is very good. </string>
    <string name="taco_loco_contact">Str. Vasile Bumbac, Nr. 5A, Suceava</string>
    <string name="taco_loco_contact2">Phone: 0748 22 00 32</string>
    <string name="taco_loco_contact3">Schedule: Monday - Sunday : NON STOP</string>
    <string name="latino_desc">This is a great restaurant! Here you can find true Romanian traditional food, very tasty! 
        Do not go there in the week-ends because is very crowded! The staff is polite, the food is all made fresh, from traditional ingredients. 
        Highly recommended for foreign visitors who want to discover the Romanian traditional food.</string>
    <string name="latino_contact">Str. Curtea Domneasca, Nr. 9, Suceava</string>
    <string name="latino_contact2">Phone: 0730920920</string>
    <string name="latino_contact3">Schedule: Monday - Sunday : 9.00 am - 23.00 pm </string>
    <string name="vama_veche_desc">At this restaurant the steak is great, the staff also, but there are some things that could be better.
         The rest of the food is ok, but not excellent and the prices are pretty high for. The desert is special.
         A fine restaurant but not the greatest.</string>
    <string name="vama_veche_contact">Str. Humorului, Nr. 87, Scheia</string>
    <string name="vama_veche_contact2">Phone: 0230 526 939</string>
    <string name="vama_veche_contact3">Schedule: Monday - Sunday: NON STOP </string>
    <string name="oscar_wilde_desc">It is a very nice restaurant, in the centre of the city. The food is great, especially the pastas, even the service is not one of the best.
         If you go there, you definitely have to try the coffee cream, the all 3 types.
	     The atmosphere is also good, the music is good, but the air is a little too smoky.</string>
    <string name="oscar_wilde_contact">Str. Ştefan cel Mare, Nr. 26, Suceava</string>
    <string name="oscar_wilde_contact2">Phone: 0330 803 102</string>
    <string name="oscar_wilde_contact3">Schedule: M-F: 8.00 am - 24.00 pm, Weekend: 11.00 am - last client</string>
    <string name="mosaik_desc">Excellent international and Romanian dishes served in a professional way. Mosaik shares a very beautiful garden with Hotel Sonnenhof.
         Just outside of the center of Suceava, this is the perfect place were you can eat and/or sleep whenever visiting the north side of Romania.
          It is easy to find cheaper, but hard to find better.</string>
    <string name="mosaik_contact">Blvd. Sofia Vicoveanca, Nr. 68, Suceava</string>
    <string name="mosaik_contact2">Phone: 0230 22 00 33 </string>
    <string name="mosaik_contact3">Schedule: Monday - Sunday: 7.00 am - 11.00 pm</string>

    <!-- HOTELS -->
    <string name="bucovina_desc">The Bucovina Hotel has an impressive tradition of over 30 years in the domain of hospitality, housing rooms in Suceava. 
        The hotel offers itself not like just a wonderful place to stay but also like an ideal place to organize conferences, symposiums, business meetings or cultural reunions.</string>
    <string name="bucovina_contact">Bulevardul Ana Ipătescu, Nr. 5, Vatra Dornei </string>
    <string name="bucovina_contact2">Phone: 0230 520 250</string>
    <string name="bucovina_contact3">Stars: **</string>
    <string name="imperium_desc">The Imperium Hotel is a place full of ospitality asured by its nice staff. If you are looking for a special and elegant
         environment, this is the perfect place. The hotel is known as "The Jewel" of the city Suceava.</string>
    <string name="imperium_contact">Bld. Sofia Vicoveanca, nr.17, Suceava </string>
    <string name="imperium_contact2">Phone: 230 211 115</string>
    <string name="imperium_contact3">Stars: ****</string>
    <string name="zamca_desc">Whether you come for business, whether you come to visit , or you simply want to relax, you have every reason to choose Zamca in Suceava.
        This place offers you a summer garden, excellent restaurants, a well mentained football field and a fully equipped games club.</string>
    <string name="zamca_contact">Strada Zamca, Nr. 28 A, Suceava </string>
    <string name="zamca_contact2">Phone: 230 521 008</string>
    <string name="zamca_contact3">Stars: ***</string>
    <string name="continental_desc">Classic with a privileged position in the city center, Continental Hotel is in proximity of the most important tourist attractions , 
        and administrative points. The hotel has the best conference rooms and reservations offer in town.</string>
    <string name="continental_contact">Str. Mihai Viteazul, Nr. 4–6, Suceava </string>
    <string name="continental_contact2">Phone: 372 304 904</string>
    <string name="continental_contact3">Stars: ***</string>
    <string name="sonnenhof_desc">The Sonnenhof Hotel welcomes guests with great services and home-like atmosphere. 
        The 58 spacious, comfortable rooms, decorated in shades of green and garden motifs will make your stay extremely relaxing.</string>
    <string name="sonnenhof_contact">Blvd. Sofia Vicoveanca, Nr. 68, Suceava </string>
    <string name="sonnenhof_contact2">Phone: 230 220 033</string>
    <string name="sonnenhof_contact3">Stars: ****</string>

    <!-- ATTRACTIONS -->
    <string name="cacica_desc">The Cacica salt mine represents an important tourist attraction of the region.
        Cacica Salt Mine is one of the oldest exploitations of salt recrystallized from brine from Europe.This is great place to spent a few days in relaxation and 
        cure at the salt mine which treats a lot of pulmonary and rheumatism diseases.</string>
    <string name="cacica_contact">18 km away from Gura Humorului, near Cacica Town.</string>
    <string name="cacica_contact2">Monday-Sunday: 09:00 – 17:00</string>
    <string name="cetate_desc">Cetatea de Scaun a Sucevei is a medieval fortress located in city of Suceava, Suceava County. It was built in 14th century  during Petru I Muşat\'s reign and expanded 
        in the 15th century during Stefan the Great III\'s reign. The citadel played a key role in Stefan the Great III of Modavia\'s defense system.</string>
    <string name="cetate_contact">Aleea Cetatii, Suceava </string>
    <string name="cetate_contact2">Monday–Friday: 17:00 – 20:00
        Saturday–Sunday: 8:00 – 20:00</string>
    <string name="porumbescu_desc">The music fans can enter the universe in which the biggest composer of Bucovina has lived. The Memorial House in which the founder of the Romanian 
        modern music has lived, is impressive not only for its oldness but for its historical importance and architectonic style.</string>
    <string name="porumbescu_contact">Stupca Village, Suceava </string>
    <string name="porumbescu_contact2">April–October/ Thusday–Sunday: 10:00 – 18:00
        October–April/ Thusday–Sunday: 9:00 – 17:00</string>
    <string name="putna_desc">The Putna Monastery is one of the most important cultural, religious and artistic centers established in medieval Moldavia.
        The Putna Monastery houses the tombs of Stefan the Great —nowadays, a place of pilgrimage —, and several of his family members. The icon veils and tombstones
         are held as fine examples of Moldavian art in Stefan the Great’s time.</string>
    <string name="putna_contact">DC47A 168, Putna Village</string>
    <string name="putna_contact2">Phone: 0230 414 055</string>
    <string name="sucevita_desc">Sucevita Monastery is an Eastern Orthodox convent built in 1585 by Ieremia Movilă, Gheorghe Movilă and Simion Movilă.
        This classic Moldavian church with its five rooms, shows the first new architectural tendencies: smaller niches, and three bases for the tower. 
        The frescoes are very remarkable, colourful and well preserved.</string>
    <string name="sucevita_contact">Sucevita Village, 18 km away from the city of Rădăuţi.</string>
    <string name="sucevita_contact2">Phone: 230 417 110</string>
    <string name="voronet_desc">The Church of St. George of the Voronet Monastery is possibly the most famous church of Romania. Often known 
        as the "Sistine Chapel of the East", the frescoes at Voroneț feature an intense shade of blue known in Romania as "Voroneț blue".</string>
    <string name="voronet_contact">6 km from Voroneț Village, Gura Humorului, Suceava County</string>
    <string name="voronet_contact2">Monday-Sunday: 7:00 – 20:00</string>

    <!-- SHOPPING -->
    <string name="iulius_desc">Iulius Mall Suceava revolutionizes the retail market through regional mix of shopping -dining -entertainment. The modern architecture and design added 
        the 150 quality brands, are recommending Iulius Mall Suceava as a top destination for shopping and entertainment with style.</string>
    <string name="iulius_contact">Calea Unirii, Nr. 22, Suceava</string>
    <string name="iulius_contact2">Phone: 0230 208 700</string>
    <string name="iulius_contact3">Monday–Sunday: 10:00 – 22:00</string>
    <string name="metro_desc">What\'s the results when you combine the sweet Moldavian mouth and the Metro professionalism? A warm 
        and familiar shop, in which the customer likes to come, and receives solutions from the Metro team, adapted to his needs.</string>
    <string name="metro_contact">Bd. 1 Decembrie 1918, Nr.5, Suceava</string>
    <string name="metro_contact2">Phone: 0230 406 150</string>
    <string name="metro_contact3">Monday–Saturday: 6:00 – 22:00 Sunday: 8:00 – 18:00</string>
    <string name="galeria_desc">On Bucovina lands, Galleria Suceava aims to combine traditions with good humour, entertainment with relaxation. Galleria Suceava offers its customers 
        a new shopping concept, a mall completely devoted to them, defined by new brands, useful services, plenty of music and fun.</string>
    <string name="galeria_contact">Strada Sofia Vicoveanca, Nr. 1, Suceava</string>
    <string name="galeria_contact2">Monday–Sunday: 9:00 – 21:00</string>
    <string name="carrefour_desc">Carrefour...Suceava...Bucovina...three words that, taken together, symbolizes tradition, variety, innovation and perspective.
        Carrefour Suceava group promotes values, such as low prices, quality, freshness, variety, innovation and service.</string>
    <string name="carrefour_contact">Calea Unirii, Nr. 27 B, Suceava</string>
    <string name="carrefour_contact2">Monday–Sunday: 8:00 – 22:00</string>
    <string name="carrefour_contact3">0374 146 200</string>

    <!-- TITLES ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="title_activity_sonnenhof">Sonnenhof Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_imperium">Imperium Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_continental">Continental Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zamca">Zamca Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bucovina">Bucovina Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cetate">Cetatea de Scaun a Sucevei</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sucevita">Sucevita Monastery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_up">Discover Suceava</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="title_activity_voronet">Voronet Monastery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_putna">Putna Monastery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cacica">The Salt Mine from Cacica</string>
    <string name="title_activity_porumbescu">Ciprian Porumbescu\'s Memorial House</string>
    <string name="title_activity_iulius">Iulius Mall</string>
    <string name="title_activity_galeria">Galeria Mall</string>
    <string name="title_activity_metro">Metro</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Suceava</string>
    <string name="title_activity_carrefour">Carrefour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food_drink">Food and Drink</string>
    <string name="title_activity_padrino">Padrino Restaurant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="title_activity_attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trip_journal">Trip Journal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_app">About Discover Suceava</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mosaik">Mosaik Restaurant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_feedback">Give Us Feedback!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_oscar_wilde">Oscar Wilde Pub</string>
    <string name="title_activity_taco_loco">Taco Loco Restaurant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_latino">Latino Restaurant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vama_veche">Vama Veche Restaurant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="title_activity_weather">Weather</string>
    <string name="journal_text">You have no entries yet in your journal. Make some memories!</string>
    <string name="grafic_button">Most visited!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grafic">Top Five Most Visited</string>
    <string name="no_user">You are not signed in !</string>
</resources>
